https://www.magicstor.com/privacy-policy.html

Log In or Register Change Currency: USDJPYGBPCADEURAUDAdvanced SearchHomePrivacy PolicyShop by CategoryHomepageMagic DVDMagic BooksEdward MarloKarrell FoxMagic BookletsComic BooksCard Tricks, Trick Cards, CardsMailing ListEnter your e-mail address to receive our newsletterYour Shopping BasketYour basket is empty.Featured ProductDiminishing Returns - Mike PowersBest SellersHarry Lorayne's Apocalypse Volumes 1 - 5Seconds, Centers, Bottoms by Ed MarloJohn Carney's CARNEYCOPIA by Stephen MinchChronicles - Karl FulvesEpilogue Hardcover – 1993 - Karl FulvesPrivacy PolicyThe Magic Shop Privacy Statement At The Magic Shop, we take your right to privacy very seriously. Our privacy policy is as follows: All Credit Card and On Line Draft information is secured on Secure Servers and is additionally Encrypted using PGP key coding. The information received is restricted to one computer and is not available to any unauthorized employee to prevent the possibility of Credit Card fraud. Unless stated otherwise, as in the case of prize drawings, giveaways, and special promotions, we never sell, give, lend, show, or otherwise share any information about our clients or visitors to our web site. The Magick Shop does not share general demographic information about our clients as a group with our partners. The Magick Shop DOES NOT share or sell your registration information to anyone outside of the company. All registration information is kept private. If you have any concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us:   About UsPrivacy PolicyContact UsTerms and Conditionskuroutohttps://www.magicstor.comcommoneCommerce by CubeCart
